(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
YouTube
★無料チラ見せ枠★
★Free Sneak Peek Slot★
差し入れを贈ってくださった皆様、本当にありがとうございます！
Thank you so much to everyone who sent gifts!
なんであなたにはできないの？
"Why can't you do it like everyone else?"
なんてさ陰口言われたり
Being talked about behind my back...
呆れられたり
...and being looked down upon.
口角下がるデイ・バイ・デイ
The corners of my mouth sag, day by day.
電車は私を置き去りに
The train leaves me behind,
しちゃうし
as it always does.
葉物野菜も
Even the leafy vegetables...
スピード速すぎだよね
...are moving way too fast.
ありのままの素敵さだけじゃ足りないんだ (Wait for me!)
Just being myself isn't enough anymore. (Wait for me!)
毎日死ぬほど頑張って
Working myself to death every day,
やっとここまで連れてきたんだ
I've finally made it this far.
あなたにはわからない
You wouldn't understand.
分かってほしくない
I don't want you to understand.
私の苦労も
My struggles and efforts...
雲ひとつほどご存知ないでいてね
I hope you remain completely unaware of them.
きっとあなたにもできるはず
"I'm sure you can do it too."
なんてさ言うほど
I don't want to be...
無責任にはなりたくない
...that irresponsible to say such things.
それでも死ぬほど頑張って
But even so, I worked myself to death,
駆ける値打ちはあると思った
thinking it was worth the chase.
投げ出したくもなるよ
There are times I want to throw it all away.
でも諦めたくはない
But I don't want to give up.
私の未来も
My future,
失敗も全部
and all my failures...
私だけのもの
...they belong to me alone.
あなたにはわからない
You wouldn't understand.
分かってほしくない
I don't want you to understand.
私の苦労も
My struggles and efforts...
雲ひとつほどご存知ないで
I hope you remain completely unaware of them.
投げ出したくもなるよ
There are times I want to throw it all away.
でも諦めたくはない
But I don't want to give up.
私の未来も
My future,
失敗も全部渡さないよ
and all my failures, I won't hand them over.
気づかない気づかないでいて
Stay unaware, please stay unaware.
可愛いだけの私でいたい
I just want to be the cute version of myself.
...アイスみたいにとろけて
...melting like ice
分かんなくなる
I'm starting not to understand
夢も愛もギュッとして
Holding dreams and love tight
いっぱいだから
Because it's full
持ちきれない
I can't hold it all
でも欲張りすぎて
But being too greedy
きっと落ちていく
I'll surely fall
もうラカラカ チュチュ 恋に落ちちゃって
Already Laka-Laka Chu-Chu, falling in love
ギュッギュッ
Tight, tight
戻れない
I can't go back
あれあれ なんでフワリと
Oh my, why so softly
心がまだ熱くなるの
My heart is still getting hot
ラカラカ チュチュ
Laka-Laka Chu-Chu
君の重力で
With your gravity
ギュッギュッ
Tight, tight
引き寄せて
Pulling me in
万華鏡を覗いてるみたいで
Like looking through a kaleidoscope
ねえねえ
Hey, hey
キラキラな未来みたい
Like a sparkling future
分かんない
I don't know
Up and down で超振り回す
Up and down, spinning me around
You and me は四六時中
You and me, 24/7
カレンダー 30日でも足りない
Even 30 days on a calendar aren't enough
あれもこれもそれも全部したい
I want to do this, that, and everything
ギュッギュッギュッ上昇 吐息百数
Gyu-gyu-gyu rise, breath count 100
ギュッギュッギュッ効果 深呼吸
Gyu-gyu-gyu effect, take a deep breath
ギュッギュッギュッ上昇 ラブメーター
Gyu-gyu-gyu rise, love meter
ギュッギュッギュッ効果 突撃だ！
Gyu-gyu-gyu effect, charge!
ときのそら New Year's Party 2026 Dreams in Motion 開演までしばらくお待ちください。
Tokino Sora New Year's Party 2026 'Dreams in Motion'. Performance starts shortly. Please wait.
バーチャル リアル どっち可愛い？
Virtual, Real, which is cuter?
バーチャル リアル どっちも可愛い！
Virtual, Real, both are cute!
サムネタップ 始めまして
Tap the thumbnail, nice to meet you
ギュンとして ならはいどうぞ
If you're feeling 'kyun', then here you go
通信は良好 いつでもカモン
Connection is good, anytime come on
一緒に踊ろよ アーネノ
Let's dance together, A-ne-no
お菓子食べたいけどダイエット中
I want to eat sweets but I'm on a diet
君の好みにアップデート中
Updating to your liking
ポチり更新 君と更新
Click and update, update with you
もっと推してほしいな
I want you to support me more
バーチャル リアル どっちが好き？
Virtual, Real, which do you like?
つながる 1 2 3次元
Connecting 1, 2, 3 dimensions
One two three で飛び越えて
One, two, three, jump over
今や夢ともリアルです
Now even dreams are real
チクチクしないで ラブピースで
Don't be prickly, with Love & Peace
ときめいちゃ
Heart-throbbing
どきがけが
My heart is...
2D + 3D は
2D + 3D is...
混ぜれば最強 バーチャルリアル
Mix them and it's the strongest, Virtual Real
二番にスワイプ ビート足して
Swipe to the second, add a beat
ギュンとして なら手叩いて
If you're feeling 'kyun', then clap your hands
勝ち勢も 負け勢も
Winners and losers alike
一緒に踊ろよ アーネノ
Let's dance together, A-ne-no
ニュー楽しいことにタッチ
Touch new fun things
ビビビテレパシー 今日も配信
Bi-bi-bi telepathy, streaming today too
もっとハグほしいな
I want more hugs
ねえねえ どっち可愛い？
Hey hey, which is cuter?
どっち可愛い？
Which is cuter?
どっちも可愛い！
Both are cute!
お菓子食べたいけどダイエット中
I want to eat sweets but I'm on a diet
君の好みにアップデート中
Updating to your liking
ポチり更新 君と更新
Click and update, update with you
もっと推してほしいな
I want you to support me more
バーチャル リアル どっちが好き？
Virtual, Real, which do you like?
バーチャル リアル どっちも好き！
Virtual, Real, I love both!
差し入れを贈ってくださった皆様、本当にありがとうございます！
To everyone who sent gifts, thank you very much!
1 2 3次元
1 2 3-dimensional
One Two Threeで飛び越えて
Leap across with a One Two Three
今やめてもリアルで
Even if I stop now, it's real
ちくちくしないでラブとピースで
Don't be prickly, with love and peace
Chu-chaku wa wa wa
ときめいちゃう
My heart's a-flutter
トキメキあげ
Giving you excitement
ツンでタスン リビンワ
Tsun de tasun ribin wa
まてれば最強
If you can wait, it's the strongest
バーチャリアラ
Virtual-ala
開演までしばらくお待ちください。
Please wait a moment until the performance begins.
Chu chu chu... chu chu chu...
Che cheri chu chu cho
イェーイ！
Yay!
僕らが見ている太陽
The sun that we are watching
八分音符のマエストロ
The eighth note maestro
実はちょっと昔らしい
Apparently it's from a while ago
そう考えると不思議かもね
When you think about it like that, it's strange
そこにあるようでいて
It seems to be right there
少し冷たい時間を過ごしてる
Yet we spend our time a little cold
きっと僕らの平行線
Surely our parallel lines
隣の人のことを
Know nothing about
一つも知らないけれど
The person right next to us
分からないまま日が沈んでいった
And the sun went down while we still didn't know
アマテラテラスこの手で
Amatera-terasu with this hand
触れて輪になって踊りましょう
Let's touch and dance in a circle
アマテラテラス聞かせて
Amatera-terasu let me hear it
あのね君だって歌えるよ
You know, even you can sing
誰にだって降り注いだ
Pouring down on everyone
八分音符の光が差す方へ
Towards the direction where the eighth note light shines
差し入れを贈ってくださった皆様、本当にありがとうございます！
To everyone who sent us gifts, thank you very much!
フラスタ [公開OK] お名前一覧
Flower Stands [Public OK] Name List
...の空を
...the sky
Come with us, dance, dance, dance, step by step
越えては闇に焼けたまま
Crossing over, still scorched in the darkness
目を醒ましても離れないで
Even if I wake up, please don't leave me
Maybe need it, 正気じゃないのよ
Maybe need it, I'm not in my right mind
太陽が忘れられない
I can't forget the sun
Colorless, そんなじゃないから
Colorless, because it's not like that
独り占めしてユフォリア
Keeping the euphoria all to myself
お弁当 [公開OK] お名前一覧
Lunch Boxes [Public OK] Name List
気にしてないような言葉は装飾で
Words that seem indifferent are just decorations
メイクのように罠流せない
I can't wash away the traps like makeup
三百六十度、偽りだって寂し切れるような
360 degrees, even if it's a lie, it's enough to feel lonely
私にかまって、Overnight crazy crazy love
Pay attention to me, Overnight crazy crazy love
待ってろ、ガラス纏わせて
Wait for me, let me wear glass
君の鼓動は、私の心臓心理を
Your heartbeat is my heart's psychology
振り返るなよ、静止しないで
Don't look back, don't stop
過ぎ去ったネオン残像、シュレディンガー
The neon afterimage that passed by, Schrödinger
スライダー みたいに漂えば、曇、曇なかった
If it floats like a slider, there were no clouds, no clouds
指先でまた、君を探している
I'm looking for you again with my fingertips
その声を聞かせてよ
Let me hear that voice
私にかまって、教えてよ恋の先を
Pay attention to me, tell me what's beyond love
広がってく彷徨うユニバース
The wandering universe is expanding
君の存在は、私の将来までも
Your existence, even my future
飛び込んだのよ、突き合わせてよね
I've jumped in, let's match up
一切合切 dance, dance, step by step、夢中になって
Everything dance, dance, step by step, becoming absorbed
リストバンド [公開OK] お名前一覧
Wristbands [Public OK] Name List
ここに宣言します、すべてを注ぎ込む
I declare here, I will pour everything in
開演までしばらくお待ちください。
Please wait a while until the performance starts.
一、病める時も 健やかなる時も ずっと
One: Whether in sickness or in health, always
愛を歌い続けることを 堂々と誓います
I solemnly swear to continue singing of love
二、歌うとかダンスも もっと追求します
Two: I will pursue singing and dancing even more
三、ずっと推してもらえるアイドルになって見せます
Three: I'll show you I can become an idol you can support forever
四、不安定な未来も 私が照らすんだ
Four: Even in an unstable future, I will light the way
それでも落ち込んじゃう日は 思い出していいよ みんなのその笑顔
Even so, on days when you feel down, it's okay to remember everyone's smiles
2026.01.10 Tokyo International Forum
January 10, 2026 Tokyo International Forum
1st year 2019
2nd year 2020
3rd year 2021
4th year 2022
5th year 2023
6th year 2024
8th year 2025
with DJ ANKIMO
Are You Ready?
Dreams in Motion New Year's Party 2026
未完成の地図を輝きに変えて
Transforming the incomplete map into brilliance
誰にも真似できない足跡を見てて
Watch these footprints that no one can imitate
みんなー！
Everyone!
走り出した願いは加速していく準備路
The wishes that started running are on the accelerating path
目に映るものに戸惑いながら
While being puzzled by the things I see
仮想世界だって私が見えてるんでしょ？
Even if it's a virtual world, you can see me, right?
君だけにある世界が正解
The world that exists only for you is the right answer
ドキドキは泣き出したくもなるよ
This heartbeat makes me want to start crying
だけどドキドキがクレッシェンド鳴り止まないから
But the pounding of my heart is a crescendo that won't stop
大きくなってだって君に届けたいよ
Even as it grows bigger, I want to reach you
素顔になってだって未来を見に行こうよ
Even by showing my true self, let's go see the future
明けない夜だって光のライヤーじゃなくて
Even in a night that doesn't break, not with a liar's light
平気だよ一緒に笑いたいから
It's okay, because I want to laugh together
綺麗になってだってちょっぴり自信持って
Even by becoming beautiful, having a little confidence
目から目だってだってここで歌いたいの
Eye to eye, I want to sing here
いつもよりもちょっと大きな声でもっと
With a voice a little louder than usual, more and more
自分信じて星型になろうね！
Believe in yourself and let's become star-shaped!
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi!
声がちょっとちっちゃいかなー？
Is your voice a little quiet?
スポットライトもうちょっと当ててきて最高潮
Shine the spotlight a little more, reaching the climax
不安も全部巻き込んでアガるステージ
Involving all anxieties, the stage heats up
星となりだってこれが私のクロール
Even as I become a star, this is my crawl
君だけに見せたいカラーの世界
A world of color I want to show only to you
みんな声出していけるかー！？
Everyone, can you shout!?
せーの！ワッショイ！
One, two! Wasshoi!
ワッショイ！ワッショイ！ワッショイ！ワッショイ！
Wasshoi! Wasshoi! Wasshoi! Wasshoi!
今日だけは一緒に泣いてもいいよ
It's okay to cry together just for today
だけど明日は自分を明るいヒトと書くようにしてね
But from tomorrow, try to see yourself as a bright person
大きく歌って 歌って 君に届けたいよ
I want to sing out loud, sing out, and reach you
夢を願って 願って 未来を見に行こうよ
Wishing for dreams, wishing for dreams, let's go see the future
夢物語だって 晴れが向かい風だって
Even if it's a fairy tale, even if the clear sky brings headwind
私たちを彩るVoiceだもん
Because it's the voice that colors us
キレイになって なって
Becoming beautiful, beautiful...
ちょびっと自信持ってね 誰だっていいよ
Have a little confidence, it's okay for anyone
君と一緒に歌いたいだけだよ
I just want to sing with you
いつもよりも誰よりも想い出ギュッと抱きしめて
Embracing memories more tightly than usual, than anyone
魔法をかけるよ さあ
I'll cast a spell, now!
せーの！ もっと！ もっと！
One, two! More! More!
はい！ はい！ はい！ はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
したたに したたに しつこくまたまた手探る
Stubbornly, stubbornly, persistently groping my way again
アンチなリズムを そうか 倒しちゃうの
So, are you going to defeat that anti-rhythm?
見過ごし千花だ シルエット 見え隠れしたそのモーション
Silhouette of a thousand flowers overlooked, that motion seen and hidden
コジツケされた 悪い悪い子まで
Even to the bad, bad children who were forced along
一連にユラユラ 開始の合図 狂うか 回れ 言い止まれよ
Swaying in succession, the signal to start. Go mad or spin, stop saying it
あっちのほうで踊りましょう 唇そのうちに
Let's dance over there, before the lips speak
もっと頂戴
Give me more
響かせたい歌いだけなの 揺れるこのキャピラリー
I just want to sing and make it ring out, this swaying capillary
霧の中 歌いだけなの 過ごした道 披露
I just want to sing in the fog, showing the path I've walked
ひとつでしょうか 星が満ちてる 砂利を伝えたいかな
Is it just one? The stars are full. Do I want to convey the gravel?
君には容赦しないわ さあ
I won't go easy on you, come on!
いなーい いなーい ばあ 捨てちゃえば またまた遊びましょう
Peek-a-boo, if you throw it away, let's play again
終わり切れない感情 瞳の中で見ててててて
Unending emotions, look into my eyes
大概な時 大概な時 コツコツ振り絞って情緒は
Most of the time, most of the time, bit by bit wringing out emotions
どうしようかな どうしようかな 暗い暗い夜の中
What should I do? What should I do? In the dark, dark night
音がもしも 私の世界に舞い落ちて
If sound should flutter down into my world
キレイになって そうでしょう
It would become beautiful, wouldn't it?
響かせたい歌いだけなの 揺れるこのキャピラリー
I just want to sing and make it ring out, this swaying capillary
霧で満たした歌いだけなの 作用する新しわ
I just want to sing filled with fog, a new action
待ってたはずよ 星が満ちてる 砂利を伝えたいかな
I must have been waiting. The stars are full. Do I want to convey the gravel?
秘密に会う術で 手を合わせ踊りましょう
With a secret way to meet, let's put our hands together and dance
いらない真実は 忘れさせてあげるから
Because I'll make you forget the truths you don't need
情熱を駆け引きに ずっと向いてなよ
Keep facing the passion in the bargaining
響かせたい歌いだけなの あれもこれも全部全部
I just want to sing and make it ring out, all of that and all of this
霧で満たした歌いだけなの 譲らない始めましょう
I just want to sing filled with fog, I won't give in, let's begin
響かせたい歌いだけなの 揺れるこのキャピラリー
I just want to sing and make it ring out, this swaying capillary
霧で満たした歌いだけなの 過ごした道 披露
I just want to sing filled with fog, showing the path I've walked
ひとつでしょうか 星が満ちてる 砂利を伝えたいかな
Is it just one? The stars are full. Do I want to convey the gravel?
君には容赦しないわ 届いた先に愛を
I won't go easy on you, love at the destination of what reached you
Okey-dokey へつらい程度
Okey-dokey, if it's just flattery,
冗談なら 笑いもしないよ
If it's a joke, I won't even laugh.
使い曖昧 どっちつかずの
In a vague, non-committal way,
蜃気楼に手伸ばした
I reached out to a mirage.
見え透いた嘘 本物の語り
Transparent lies, a real story,
そんな分かり合いたいフリしてた
I was pretending to want to understand like that.
散々だったこの後
After all that trouble,
まだいかないで
don't go yet.
守る術はないよ
There's no way to protect myself,
私を奪って
so take me away.
身勝手な 感情たちは
Selfish emotions,
広がっても 止まんないっすか
even if they spread, won't they stop?
君の言動は 私の真相に
Your words and actions have put a gem
かけちゃった 宝石に キミだね
on my true feelings, it's you.
さあ さあ さあ 乱して
Come, come, come, mess me up,
私を信じだって カラミあった
even if you believe in me, tangled up,
カラカラ 満ちて
drying up, getting full.
ほら ほら ほら
Look, look, look,
ダンス ダンス ダンス
dance, dance, dance,
ジャンプ ジャンプ ジャンプ
jump, jump, jump,
声は ギャン ギャン ギャン そのまま
voices screaming, just like that.
目を覚ましても 離れないで
Even if I wake up, don't leave me.
正味じゃないよ 頼る術は
It's not real, I can't come to like
好きになれない
the way of relying on things.
バカ言え バカ言え
Don't be silly, don't be silly,
そんなんじゃないから
it's not like that,
衝動に身を任せて ボリヤー
so just give yourself over to the impulse, Boliya!
気にしてないよな 合図を待って
I'm not bothered by it, waiting for the signal,
迷路のように抗えない
unable to resist like a maze.
散々だった この空
The sky was terrible,
まだいかないで
don't go yet.
寂しすぎるよな
It's too lonely,
私に構って
pay attention to me.
身勝手な 感情たちは
Selfish emotions,
広がっても 止まんないっすか
even if they spread, won't they stop?
君の言動は 私の真相に
Your words and actions have put a gem
かけちゃった 宝石に キミだね
on my true feelings, it's you.
過ぎ去った ネオンを糧にした
I've made the past neon lights my food.
スライダーみたいに漂えば
If I drift like a slider,
肯定も否定もなかった
there was neither affirmation nor negation.
指先でまた 君を探している
Searching for you again with my fingertips,
その声を聞かせてよ
let me hear that voice.
私に構って
Pay attention to me,
教えてよ 恋の先を
tell me what's beyond love,
広がっても 止まんないっすか
even if it spreads, won't it stop?
君の存在は 私の将来まで
Your existence has put a gem
かけちゃった 宝石に キミだね
even on my future, it's you.
さあ さあ さあ 乱して
Come, come, come, mess me up,
私を信じだって カラミあった
even if you believe in me, tangled up,
カラカラ 満ちて
drying up, getting full.
ほら ほら ほら
Look, look, look,
ダンス ダンス ダンス
dance, dance, dance,
ジャンプ ジャンプ ジャンプ
jump, jump, jump,
声は ギャン ギャン ギャン そのまま
voices screaming, just like that.
目を覚ましても 離れないで
Even if I wake up, don't leave me.
イエーイ！
Yeah!
皆さん、新年あけましておめでとうございます！
Everyone, Happy New Year!
イエーイ！
Yeah!
盛り上がってますかー？
Are you all hyped up?
みんなで協力して、優しい気持ちでライブできてるかにょ？
Is everyone working together and enjoying the live with kind feelings?
いいねー、素晴らしいよ。ふふふ。
Nice, that's wonderful. Hehe.
みんな見えてるよ。今日はみんな青いんだね。
I can see everyone. Everyone is blue today.
ちょっとあれか、あのTシャツ、Tシャツが...今着てくれてる人？
Is it because of that T-shirt? The person wearing that T-shirt now?
おおー。待って、当日券買ってくれた人っていますか？
Oh! Wait, is there anyone who bought a same-day ticket?
おおー。ありがとうございます。感動した！
Oh! Thank you. I'm moved!
ありがとうございます、本当に嬉しいです。
Thank you, I'm really happy.
ということでね、やりました、あれをやりましょうか。えー、そうですね。
So, we did it, let's do that thing. Hmm, let's see.
遠くから来てくれた人！
People who came from far away!
そうだよね、飛行機とかで来てくれた人いたもんね。
Right, there were people who came by plane and such.
じゃあ、海外ニキニキ！
Then, overseas fans!
うおーー！
Whoa!
じゃあ、声は出さなくてもいい、あの、ペンライト、クルクルやるだけでもいいよ。
Then, you don't have to shout, it's okay just to twirl your penlight.
女の子ー！
Girls!
ありがとー！前の方でぴょんぴょん飛んでるの、見えたよ。めちゃくちゃピコピコしてる。
Thank you! I saw you jumping around in the front. You're moving so much.
奥の方の子も見えてるよ。大声ありがとうございます！
I can see the girls in the back too. Thank you for the loud voices!
そして、2階席ー！
And, the 2nd floor balcony!
1階席ー！
The 1st floor!
じゃあ、またペンライト遊びしちゃおう。
Well then, let's play with our penlights again.
左の人、緑ー！
Everyone on the left, change to green!
右の人は、じゃあ、オレンジ！
How about everyone on the right... change to orange!
じゃあ、真ん中は青ー！
And everyone in the center, change to blue!
うわー、綺麗だー！
Whoa, it's beautiful!
みんな、今回はね、こんな感じで、みんなも演出に参加しちゃうライブになっているよ。
Everyone, this concert is designed so that you can participate in the production like this.
みんなで楽しんでいこうねー！
Let's all have a great time together!
今日はみんなも主役なんだー！
You're all the stars of the show today!
おいし、おいしいから...
It's good... It tastes good...
夜はね、いっぱい動くと思って、まあ、もう動いてるけど、昼から飲めばよかった。
I thought I'd be moving around a lot tonight—well, I already am—but I should've started drinking it this afternoon.
踊り一択。
It's all about dancing.
ガッツリ。今日、今年の目標、ムキムキになっていこうと思いました。
Definitely. My goal for this year... I decided to get totally ripped.
頑張れ！
Good luck!
というわけで、じゃあ、初めての人ー！
Anyway, who's here for the first time?
じゃあ、これ、拍手してくれてありがとうございます。
Well, thank you all for the applause.
一番最初のライブから全部来てるよって人いる？
Is there anyone here who's been to every single concert since the very first one?
うおー！ありがとうございます。
Whoa! Thank you so much.
というわけでね、みんな分かったね。初めましての人も、いつも空友様の人も、
So, as you can see, whether you're here for the first time, or you're a long-time Sora-tomo...
そして、昔から応援してる人、みんな集まって、みんなが、空友だよ。
or you've been supporting me since the beginning, we're all here together, and you're all Sora-tomos.
みんな、楽しく過ごしていこうねー！
Let's all have a wonderful time!
というわけで、なんと、YouTubeでの無料配信、あ、全然言ってないのに...
And now... believe it or not, the free stream on YouTube... Oh, I haven't even mentioned it yet...
まだ、来たばっかり、まだ来たばっかりかと思うけど、続きは概要欄から...
I know you've only just arrived, but you can catch the rest of the show via the link in the description...
えー、いえーいの人はどうしたらいいの？
Wait, what should the 'Yay!' people do?
ごめん、あ、コメント会場、配信会場の人も楽しんでってねー！
Sorry! To everyone watching in the comments and on the stream, keep having fun!
それでは、もう一回飲んでから行くね。水分も大事。
Well then, I'll take one more drink before we continue. Staying hydrated is important.
助かる、助かってくれてありがとう。
That helps... thank you for the 'Tasugaru'.
では、次の曲も楽しんでいってね！
Now, please enjoy the next song!
まだ、ほんのちょっと、足りないな、し、く...
It's still just a little bit... not enough...
冒頭無料配信はこちらで終了です。
The introductory free stream ends here.
The free preview ends here.
続きは、Z-aNにてお楽しみください。
Please enjoy the rest on Z-aN.
ありがとうございました。
Thank you very much.